ionair.tv 2012-06-15

# Watch OnAir TV, Dramas, Music Videos and Movies for Free! - iOnAir.tv

This privacy policy applies to the information iOnAir.TV (hereinafter iOnAir) collects about you as a user of iOnAir. This policy does not apply to information about you collected by third party websites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from iOnAir. The information collected or received by third parties is subject to their own privacy policies. 

Information We Collect About You

We collect or receive information about you when you interact with iOnAir. Registering with iOnAir is optional and we may collect information even if you do not register. Depending on how you use our services, your information may include:

• registration-related information (such as name, e-mail address, age, preferred language, or gender);   
• information about how frequently you use our services; your responses to the advertisements presented on iOnAir or other features made available by iOnAir, including those available on third party websites;   
• information about the searches you perform through iOnAir and how you use the results of those searches;   
• customer service information about you as an iOnAir user;   
• location data and other information about mobile devices used to access and interact with iOnAir; or   
• other information specifically related to your use of our services including information that you publicly post using tools made available by iOnAir. 

Your information may be supplemented with additional information from other companies such as publicly available information, information about households, and other information which we may append or match to your iOnAir information.

iOnAir may also receive or collect certain technical information when you use our services. This may include: the type of browser or operating system you are using, your manner of connecting to the Internet and the name of your Internet service provider; your Internet protocol address; information about iOnAir services that you used prior to registering with iOnAir; and data relating to computer malfunctions or problems occurring when you use your computer with our services. Additionally, we may collect information about other software on your computer for the limited purpose of protecting your security or improving your online experience.

How We Use the Information We Collect

Your information is used for purposes that include: 

  * • to operate and improve the sites, services, and offerings available through iOnAir;
  * • to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you (including to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers);
  * • to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services;
  * • to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries;
  * • to perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. 
  * • to manage our business; 
  * • to conduct research about your use of iOnAir; and
  * • to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest.

iOnAir may use cookies, web beacons, or other technologies in combination with your iOnAir information to enhance and personalize your experience on iOnAir. 

With Whom We Share Your Information

iOnAir does not rent or sell your information (such as name, gender, age and id) to third parties for their marketing purposes. iOnAir may share your information with third parties to provide products and services you have requested, when we have your consent, or as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Your iOnAir information may be shared with sites and services subject to this Privacy Policy. You may have choices about collection and use of your iOnAir information. 

The contents of your online communications, as well as other information about you as an iOnAir user, may be accessed and disclosed in response: to lawful governmental requests or legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena), in other circumstances in which iOnAir has a good faith belief that a crime has been or is being committed by an iOnAir user, that an emergency exists that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person, when necessary either to protect the rights or property of iOnAir, or for us to render the service you have requested. 

iOnAir’s offerings may include features or functionalities provided by third parties. In the process of providing such functionalities within iOnAir services, your browser may automatically send certain technical information to the third party provider. The use of these third-party provided features or functionalities is subject to their own privacy policies. 

Business partners or other third parties may receive data about groups of iOnAir users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you. 

We may use agents and contractors in order to help operate iOnAir. Their use of information is limited to these purposes. 

In the event that ownership of iOnAir was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition, or transfer to another company, your iOnAir information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your iOnAir information, you will be provided notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer. 

Social Networking Services

iOnAir enables you to connect with certain third-party social networking services through the iOnAir. With your consent, we may share information about your activities on iOnAir with those services and their users. This section provides information on this sharing.

• If you connect with one of these services, you may be able to publish information about your activities on iOnAir, such as your comments or the videos you watch, to that service. Please note that when you choose to publish your information from iOnAir or another website or platform to social networking services, that information will be visible to users of those services, in accordance with applicable law and the privacy policies of those services. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the services’ privacy policies and privacy controls. 

• In addition, if you visit iOnAir while logged into one of these services, the third-party service provider may be able to identify you and to associate the technical information provided by your web browser with other information the service already has about you. 

Display of Advertising

Your iOnAir information may be used for the presentation of advertisements. iOnAir may use ad networks to customize and display advertising on iOnAir. iOnAir may share certain information about you as a user (such as age, gender, or other information we have collected or received) with certain ad network and service providers to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. 

Your Choices about Your iOnAir Information

• iOnAir provides you with access to your registration information, and the ability to edit this information;   
• As an iOnAir user you may be given a choice as to whether you want to receive email messages and/or newsletters about product updates, improvements, special offers, or containing special distributions of content by iOnAir. At any time you can choose to no longer receive such notifications. iOnAir may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that, changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from iOnAir. 

Our Commitment to Security

iOnAir has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your iOnAir information, but cannot guarantee that your information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of iOnAir and its affiliated providers). To protect your privacy and security, we may use passwords to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your iOnAir information. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information

iOnAir may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to iOnAir’s information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from iOnAir as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future. 

How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the iOnAir Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us by email or postal mail as follows:

**iOnAir.TV**  
#210-19567 Fraser Hwy  
Surrey, BC V3S 9A4  
[mail@twinm.com](mailto:mail@twinm.com).
